# Cristian Maximiliano Savino

## Full Stack Web Developer

EU CITIZEN
13 Pim Street - Dublin 8
Co. Dublin, Ireland
(34) 625941020
savinocristian89@gmail.com

## PERSONAL PROFILE

I'm a highly motivated individual with good communication skills, capable of performing as a team member or alone on projects.

Throughout my career I have worked on many projects with multiple languages and technologies like PHP, Laravel, Symfony, JavaScript, TypeScript, Angular, Node.JS, Python, Docker, Dart, Flutter, GIT and others.

#### PROJECT EXPERIENCE

 MrMovy - <a href="https://github.com/Crissavino/mrmovy\_laravel">https://github.com/Crissavino/mrmovy\_laravel</a> - PHP, Laravel, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, SQL, jQuery - Freelance

This is one of my first projects. It is a web app that recommends movies based on your personal tastes. You have to complete a series of questions and based on that it recommends 3 (or more) movies within the 100 best according to IMDB.

Re Faciles - <a href="https://github.com/Crissavino/refaciles">https://github.com/Crissavino/refaciles</a> - PHP, Laravel, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, SQL, jQuery - Freelance

This is a project for a girl who had an instagram of recipes with many followers and wanted to make a blog where she can upload her recipes and exchange opinions with her clients.

Genoveva - <a href="https://github.com/Crissavino/genovevaFE">https://github.com/Crissavino/genovevaFE</a> - PHP, Laravel, Angular, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, SQL, jQuery - Freelance

This is an e-commerce project carried out for a group of girls who sold clothes through instagram with more than 30 thousand followers. separate the frontend (Angular) and the backend (Laravel) by performing an API to be consumed from the front. You can see it at <a href="https://genovevaok.com">https://genovevaok.com</a>

Digital input application for victims of trafficking in persons https://github.com/Crissavino/app\_trata - PHP, Laravel, JavaScript,

 HTML5, CSS3, SQL, jQuery - Ministry of Justice of the Province of Buenos Aires, Argentina

This is a project developed for the Ministry of Justice of the Province of Buenos Aires, Argentina. Given the growing problem of trafficking in persons in the province, it was necessary to have an entry system for the victims rescued in police raids. It consists of many forms of personal data for the victim's entry and several heat maps generated with the data provided to be able to draw a potential danger zone.

 Maria Celina Romero Mc Intosh Psicologa https://github.com/Crissavino/celina.github.io - Node.JS - Freelance

This is a website that is under development for a psychologist with many patients from Fuengirola, Malaga, Spain. By which patients in addition to knowing more about the professional can book a call to make an interview by phone.

Padelmanager - <a href="https://padelmanager.com">https://padelmanager.com</a> - PHP, Laravel, JavaScript,
 HTML5, CSS3, SQL, ¡Query, Angular - Malaga, Spain

I was working in this exciting sports startup. Where amateur paddle players can see their ranking and tournaments in which they participate that are managed from the web by the clubs. My tasks were several, such as, for example, supporting the Mobile APP backend, developing new functionalities for the web administration that the clubs have on their administrator boards, and new developments. I always tried to contribute new ideas and implement technologies that perhaps were not being applied before, Angular is an example

EJI Villarreal - <a href="https://github.com/Crissavino/villarreal">https://github.com/Crissavino/villarreal</a> <a href="https://ejivillarreal.com">https://ejivillarreal.com</a> - PHP, Laravel, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, SQL, jQuery - Freelance

In this project, what the client wants is a contact website where people seeking legal advice can find it. Also how much of a blog with a dashboard where you can upload and edit notes and their tags.

• Rocknet LTD - https://rocknetItd.com/ - Dublin, Ireland

I'm currently working in Rocknet. Here we create easy, intuitive and massive web applications which we monetize. We use the PHP framework, cakePHP, MAMP / XAMP / WAMP, JavaScript, Bootstrap, AmazonS3, user file managers such as FileRun among many other technologies and tools.

## **Work Experience**

## Rocknet, Dublin - Full Stack Developer

NOVEMBER 2020 - PRESENT

- I am responsible for creating new web apps that the owners require.
- I deploy in production at the end of every task via FTP.
- Mainly I work alone, weekly I make a sample of what has been done to the managers.

## Padelmanager, Malaga - Full Stack Developer

DECEMBER 2019 - NOVEMBER 2020

- I was responsible for supporting the platform that is already in use, both for the web and mobile.
- I was in charge of making the deployments in production at the end of the Sprints.
- Together with the team of developers we take care of carrying out the new projects that the product owners request of us.

## Freelance - Web Developer

SEPTEMBER 2018 - PRESENT

- As a freelance developer I am fully in charge of the entire process of creation and deployment in production of the requested product.
- I do both developments both on the front-end side as well as on the back-end.
- I also advise clients with the technologies that I consider necessary for each development.

## Professor - Logiscool

OCTOBER 2019 - FEBRUARY 2020

- I was teaching a block programming course to a group of children in which the objective was to make web games.
- Every week I prepare each class so that the children can go home with the game finished.

## Consultant - Dirección General de Cultura y Educación (DGCYE)

**AUGUST 2016 - AUGUST 2018** 

- I was an active part of the logistics and management team for the implementation of the National School Connectivity Plan, this plan consists of bringing Internet and a Cisco Meraki technological floor to more than 8,000 educational establishments in the province of Buenos Aires.
- I was mainly in charge of the logistics part, coordinating the installations with institutions and companies. Around 300 weekly installations were carried out.

## Secretary - CR Construcciones S.A

JANUARY 2013 - JULY 2016

- I worked as personal secretary to the president of the company.
- I handled the payments and collections of the company both in the private sector and also in the public part.
- I also had staff in charge with whom we organized the documentation and other papers to deliver in public and private bidding in which we competed.

#### Technician - Citarella S.A.

JANUARY 2007 - JULY 2007

- Performed the PC assembly for tenders, the installation of operating systems and packages that were required according to them.
- I also solved and advised simple software problems in general.

## **Education**

## Digital House, Buenos Aires - Full Stack Web Developer

MAY 2018 - DECEMBER DE 2018

**Udemy** - Angular

JULY 2019

In this course I acquired a solid base to work with Angular, apply the concepts of ECMAScript 6 in projects, create basic applications with Ionic, learn TypeScript from scratch to create applications with Angular, create them following good practices and mastering directives, pipes, components, services and structuring each application in the best way.

**Udemy** - Flutter: Your complete development guide for iOS and Android
JUNE 2020

In this course I was learning about Dart from scratch, I also understood the fundamental concepts to carry out any app design, I learned to carry out the deployment of stores, use the Flutter SDK to make applications and master a large number of Widgets.

**Udemy** - Flutter: Take your knowledge to the next level OCTOBER 2020

The course has robust structures both in the Frontend (Flutter) and in the Backend (Mainly Node), which will help us to create all the applications and manage the centralized information, it also has deployments of our APIS and Socket Server to perform the real tests on devices and have full control of authentication through social networks.

Another objective of the course is to help you lose your fear of patterns like BLoC so that we can appreciate the potential and its power without losing control of the state at any time.

By the end of the course, you will have created real-time tracking applications, chats, collections, authentications, backend, mastering BLoC and other status managers, password encryption, user session management, Apple and Google sign-in and much more. that you will need when you want to create an application that requires one or all of these technologies.

## **Skills**

## Languages

- Native European Spanish
- Intermediate/advanced knowledge of English
- Basic knowledge of Italian

#### Leadership

Skills for teamwork and ease of people management

Versatility and rapid adaptation to different tasks and work environments

Intermediate/advanced knowledge of AutoCad, Office Package and the corresponding ones in macOS